Viewers, wherever you are,
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
I say to you,
declare your stand,
"I am a child of God".
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
You are a child of God by the Spirit of God.
I am a child of God by the Spirit of Father.
I am a child of God by the Spirit of God.
Right now, I declare satan to leave you,
in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
All evil,
pain,
nightmare,
leave my people!
You, demon, leave my people!
Leave my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
Declare your stand, "I am a child of God".
I am a child of God!
By the Spirit of God,
In the name of Jesus,
leave my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
Viewers,
I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Demon, loose your grip, in the name of Jesus!
Loose your grip, in the name of Jesus!
Signs of Demons,
voice of demons,
be ceased, in the name of Jesus!
In your career, be ceased!
In your business, be ceased!
In your family, be ceased!
In your future, be ceased!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world,
where can we go from His presence?
Wherever sickness is located,
wherever disease is located,
wherever infirmity is located,
I say, out!
Out!
Out of your organs!
Out of your faculties!
Out!
The way out has come!
I command that disease, out!
I command that fibroid, out!
In your kidney,
in your bone,
in your liver,
in your blood,
I say, out!
Say, out!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name
Viewers,
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
you are here; we are there.
Whatever you might have taken or eaten in the dream
or drank on the table of your enemy,
I command them out of your system!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
I command them out of your organs!
I say, out!
Whatever you might have taken or eaten in the dream
on the table of your enemy, that is giving you pain,
limitation,
disappointment,
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith in Jesus' Name